# SEAN WILLIAMS

## UI/UX DESIGNER

(505)238-6429 sylkicks1@gmail.com

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### DIGITAL MEDIA AND YOUTH DIRECTOR

- \* Design websites, advertising material and other digital/material resources to create a relevant and meaningful program.
- \* Mentoring and creating curriculum for Middle Schoolers, High Schoolers, and Young Adults.
- Implement a variety of digital tools to engage today's youth.

#### MIDDLE SCHOOL TEACHER

Annunciation Catholic School/ Harrison Middle School

Aug 2014-July 2017

- \* Taught 6th/7th Grade Standards-Based Language Arts, Social Studies, Literature, and Journalism.
- \* Assisted in implementing school-wide technology initiatives including iPad rollout and e-classroom resources.
- Researched and created sections of master document for WCEA accreditation process.
- Served on a WCEA certification team for other area schools.

## DELIVERY DRIVER/CELLERMAN

Marble Brewery

Feb 2013-Aug 2014

- \* Delivered orders on-time on a self-made schedule.
- Worked fulfilling orders in a faced-paced brewhouse.

#### MARKETING AND PROGRAMS ASSISTANT

Ghost Ranch Education and Retreat Center

Aug 2012-May 2013

- In charge of writing copy and creating/submitting advertisements to local magazines, agencies and more.
- Served as Dean for a January Term for students from colleges around the US.
- Compiled/created material including photos and copy for course catalogs.

## **PROFILE**

As a UI/UX Designer, I seek to marry a love of tech and design with a dedication towards serving the greater good. For the past six years I served as an educator and wish to bring this rich experience to my design work.

In my free time I enjoy rock climbing, good books, good coffee, bad horror movies, and a healthy Star Wars obsession.

## **EDUCATION**

#### CAREERFOUNDRY

UI Design Certification

February-December 2020

# CENTRAL NEW MEXICO COMMUNITY COLLEGE

Secondary Education Certification

2014-2015

#### University Of New Mexico

BA Media Arts

2008-2012

## **SKILLS**

#### **PROGRAMS**

Sketch, Adobe Suite (XD, Photoshop, After Effects, Illustrator, Lightroom, etc.), Final Cut Pro, Microsoft Office, InVision, Flinto,

## UI/UX Design

Wireframing, User Personas, Research, Testing and Flows, Prototyping, Copy Writing, Visual Design